[Music] I did
[Música]
n't think it was going to be necessary but
no pensaba que iba a ser necesario pero
I'm making this video to clarify a few
hago este vídeo para aclarar unas
things. I am a content creator hergo.
cosillas soy creadora de contenido hergo
My content is for entertainment. I do not talk
mi contenido es para entretener no hablo
about my current experiences or throw it at
de mis vivencias actuales ni lanzas a
anyone because this is not the account, in other words,
nadie porque esto no es la cuenta o sea
this text that has been put to
este texto que se le ha puesto para Que
appear. The thumbnail of textto and
aparezca La miniatura de textto y todo
everyone between personal is a
el mundo entre personal es una cuenta
professional account more or less and all the
profesional más o menos y todas las
occurrences that I tell are based on
ocurrencias que cuento están basadas en
things from my very past or on things
cosas de mi pasado muy pasado o en cosas
that my friends tell me in which I am
que me cuentan mis amigos en las cuales
inspired. I have always been a
me inspiro yo siempre he sido una
very private and very reserved person at
persona muy privada y muy reservada a
16 free bullying eh I have had very
los 16 free bullying eh he tenido muy
bad luck with friendships and well,
mala suerte con las amistades y pues a
based on blows I have learned to have
base de palos he aprendido a tener muy
very few friends and talk about my private things with people who would really put their hand in the game. With that I mean, do not believe anything that is said about me on the internet and less if you come from a gossip account, you want to browse the internet safely and also
forma segura en internet y además
access all the content of your
acceder a todo el contenido de tus
favorite platforms like Netflix, HBO
plataformas favoritas como Netflix hbo
Max or Disney Plus, Cyber ​​Ghost VPN And it is  I do
Max o Disney Plus Cyber Ghost VPN Y es
n't know if you know but there is
que no sé si lo sabes pero hay
content that is not available in your country
contenidos que en tu país no están
and with this little trick you can
disponibles y con este truquillo puedes
access all the content wherever you are I do
acceder a todo el contenido estés donde
n't know if you know what a VPN is
estés no sé si sabes lo que es una VPN
but it's an extension that you put on your
pero es una extensión que le pones a tu
internet with which it masks the IP and
internet con la que enmascara la IP y
apart from browsing completely safe and
aparte de Navegar completamente seguro y
anonymous without anyone being able to know who you
anónimo sin que nadie pueda saber quién
are and where you are It helps you access
eres y dónde estás Te sirve para acceder
some content that is
a algunos contenidos que están
blocked in your country there are movies and
bloqueados en tu país hay películas y
series on your favorite platforms that are
series en tus plataformas favoritas que
not available there are
no están disponibles hay programas de
television programs for example on mediaset
televisión por ejemplo en mediaset
content that if you try to watch them outside
contenidos que si los intentas ver fuera
of Spain they have a geoblock that doesn't
de España tienen un geobloqueo que no te
allow you Well with Cyber ​​Ghost VPN that's
lo permite Pues con Cyber Ghost VPN eso
over Apart from being protected
se acabó Aparte de estar protegido
browsing under the anon anato you will be able to
navegando bajo el anón anato podrás
access the content of the entire
acceder a los contenidos de todo el
planet you will also have Total privacy
planeta además tendrás privacidad Total
since it keeps your connection private and
ya que mantiene tu conexión en privado y
protects your data ultra-fast speed
protege tus datos velocidad ultrarápida
to eliminate the lake in any
para eliminar el lago en cualquier juego
online game with which you can enjoy
online con los que podrás disfrutar de
live without interruptions and as I have already
directos sin interrupciones y como ya os
told you Freedom to access all the
he dicho Libertad para acceder a todo el
content of the planet wherever and whenever
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
you want also take advantage of a 83%
quieras además aprovecha tod un 83 por
discount using the link that I
de descuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video  and be
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
careful because you can try cyberg VPN for 45
ojo porque puedes probar cyberg VPN 45
days without obligation and if you are not convinced you can
días sin compromiso y si no te convence
ask for a refund and they will return the piece
pides el reembolso y te devuelven la pza
So do not wait any longer to protect your
Así que no esperes más para proteger tu
connection and improve your
conexión y aumentar tu experiencia en
internet experience run and click on the link in
internet corre y al click al enlace de
the description and take advantage of this super
la descripción y aprovecha esta super
cyberghost VPN offer to browse
oferta cyberghost VPN para navegar
completely free and secure I do not have
completamente libre y seguro no tengo
friends who are content creators
amigos que sean creadores de contenido
Yes I know some but that does not mean
Sí conozco algunos pero eso no significa
that I will ever tell them about my life my
que les hable de mi vida jamás mis
friends are real people completely
amigos son gente real completamente
alien to this world and that is what
ajena a este mundillo y eso es lo que me
allows me to have my why any
permite tener mi por la cual cualquier
information that comes from someone
información que venga de alguien
saying they are my friend I can tell you that it
diciendo ser mi amigo ya os digo yo que
is completely false but Who
es completamente falsa de pero Quién ha
said that they were your friend or rather Who has come
dicho que era su amigo o sea Quién ha
out saying something as if they were your
salido contando algo como si fuera su
friend now from a month ago or in
amigo ahora de hace un mes o dentro de
a year I do not care I mean I have the
un año me da igual o sea tengo los
same friends that I had a year ago and I
mismos amigos que tenía hace un año y
will continue to have them because how
los seguiré teniendo porque cómo nos ha
Ray has left us without content eh how
dejado el Ray sin content eh cómo nos ha
Ray has left us here that we could have had
dejado el Ray aquí que podríamos haber
a debate Cool eh And he has
tenido un debatio Guay eh Y nos ha
left us without content eh he has posted something on
dejado sin content eh ha puesto algo en
Twitter or something or what And they are the best and
Twitter o algo o qué Y son los mejores y
I never  they would sell it not for me eh
jamás me venderían que no sea por mí eh
family for me that it is not eh indirect
familia por mí que no quede eh indirecta
for Javi but I have not said anything about
para Javi pero yo no he dicho nada de
having a source Oh sure Well I don't
que tenga una fuente Ah claro Bueno no
know it could be it's that I don't know what
sé podría ser es que no sé qué es lo que
fake put remember that here you saw it
puso fake recuerda que aquí lo viste
first reb begs gata for a second
primero reb le suplica una segunda
chance rebor would be
oportunidad a gata rebor estaría
suffering from I don't know what this is what is
sufriendo una no sé qué es esto lo que
known as an obsession with the
se conoce como una obsesión por la
dependence of a person hence
dependencia de una persona de ahí la
rebor's attitude what she tells fy to me They
actitud de rebor esto que cuenta fy a mí
tell me that it is like this
Me comentan que es así
eh what a disgusting community I have man this
eh qué asco de comunidad tengo tío este
clip of gata if it is Indira tells me I
clip de gata si es Indira me dice os
bring you exclusively the reason why
traigo en exclusiva el motivo por el
gata and rebon have broken up But before
cual gata y rebon han roto Pero antes
Follow me for more gossip I have contact
Síganme para más salseos tengo contacto
with someone but I don't think it's me
con alguien pero yo no creo que sea mí
eh I think it's Antena 3 is
eh yo creo que es Antena 3 está
extremely close to the two who has
extremadamente cerc de los dos que me ha
verified to me that the information is
verificado que la información es
correct we have exclusive access to the witness
correcta tenemos en exclusiva al testigo
who is evacuating the breakup and who
que está evacuando la ruptura y que se
found out absolutely everything but before
enteró absolutamente de todo pero antes
showing you I'll give you a little res it all
de mostraros os hago un pequeño res todo
started on New Year's Eve when Mr. re
empezó en noche vieja cuando el señor re
went to the supermarket to see This  yes it has
fue al supermercado a ver Esto sí tiene
a little painted oliveira no and I buy
un poco pintado oliveira no y compro
grapes with I think that gata is going to give us
uvas con yo creo que gata nos va a dar
many great moments eh I mean bticino that
muchos momentazos eh o sea bticino que
gata could be one of the protagonists
gata podría ser una de las protagonistas
of 2025 Eh yes This one does look like
del 2025 Eh sí Este sí tiene pinta de
Javi oliveira but well let's see with
ser a Javi oliveira pero bueno a ver con
love eh with love with love always
cariño eh con cariño con cariño siempre
Eh it's giving me a little cring no
Eh me está dando un poco de cring no
but let's see gata I know when the
pero a ver gata se cuando ya se termine
fighting with the rebot bu is over these two are
de pelear con el rebot bu estos dos nos
going to give us some crazy cinema it's because of you the
van a dar un cine que flipa es por ti
couple you're talking about is separating
pareja de la que hablas se separa
georgio don't tell me your life either
georgio no me cuentes tu vida tampoco
worth it or else the truth is that I
vale o sea que es que la verdad que me
find it regrettable the truth is that I
parece lamentable la verdad es que me
find it regrettable no no no no no they just
parece lamentable no no no no no me
sent me the sticker for the
acaban de pasar el sticker para el grupo
WhatsApp group do you want it do you want the
de WhatsApp lo queréis queréis el
sticker for the WhatsApp group no
sticker para el grupo de WhatsApp no
well come on like this I'll send it to the
bueno venga va así lo mando al grupo de
WhatsApp group okay whoever is not in the
WhatsApp vale quien no esté en el grupo
WhatsApp group it's taking too long
de WhatsApp ya está tardando
don't put the link there put the
no poner por ahí el enlace poner por ahí
link there What is the group number it
el enlace Cuál es el número del grupo no
's not a number put the link there I know so
es un número poner por ahí el enlace se
people can enter  Hey, how many people
para que la gente entre Oye Cuánta Peña
are in the WhatsApp group 3515, put
hay en el grupo de WhatsApp 3515 poner
the group there? Look, wizard is putting it there.
por ahí el grupo Mira por ahí lo está
Run, come in, you're
poniendo wizard corre entra que te vas a
going to get a sticker. Good,
que te vas a llevar un sticker bueno
good, good for you, for your WhatsApp with
bueno bueno para tu para tu WhatsApp con
nuggets, the cat would have explicitly asked him
pepitas gata le habría pedido
without nuggets And that caused
explícitamente sin pepitas Y eso provocó
their breakup. One second they tell me through
su ruptura un segundo que me dicen por
the earpiece that the subject is in the
el pinganillo que el sujeto está en el
bathroom. Is the witness ready? Please
baño está el testigo listo por favor
come in, Mr. Phoenix. Would you have any
Pase señor Fénix tendría alguna
relevant information? Add all
información relevante que Añadir todo
that. You say what else would you add about the
eso dice usted qué más añadiría de la
breakup, Mr. Phoenix? Is it true, guys?
ruptura señor Fénix es cierto chicos
Even news reports about the
hasta informativo de noticias del
invention. Thanks, good. Oh look, you
invento Gracias bueno Ay mira lo
should open it the same. Well, hey,
tendrías que abierto lo mismo Bueno oye
everyone believes its content as they can, for
cada uno cre Su contenido como puede por
an exclusive, return the cat. They say out
una exclusiva devuelve el gato dicen por
there, what the [ __ ] do I understand that the
ahí qué [__] entiendo que las cuentas
gossip accounts need to be invented? Hey, how
de salseo necesitan inventarse Oye cómo
we missed the gossip about
nos hemos perdido el chisme de la madre
my father's mother giving it to Guibel, eh, I mean, I don't
de mi adre dando la guibel eh o sea no
understand. Why not, because if she's
entiendo el Por qué no porque si está
insulting him all day, okay? And I have
todo el día insultándolo vale Y tengo
ttas here that are tremendous. Why did she
aquí ttas que son tremendos Por qué ha
delete that, telling Guibel everything, I
borrado eso diciéndole de todo a guibel
mean  why did she delete that what would have to be done Would
o sea por qué ha borrado eso qué es lo
n't she want to be
que habría que No querría ella que se le
answered or to be touched again I don't know
conteste o que se vuelva a tocar no sé
what it would be man it's that she knows I
qué es lo que sería tío es que ella se
think she was like getting excited
yo creo que estaba como ilusionándome
that they could be against her dala
que pueden estar es en contra her dala
but it's that your story either
pero es que vuestra historia tampoco
now you didn't take a screenshot Karime you didn't
ahora no sacaste captura Karime no
do your job well Hey and the other
hiciste tu trabajo bien Oye y la otra
Karime said something else said something else the
Karime dijo algo más dijo algo más la
other or what after after that
otra o qué después de después de aquello
other day or what they have me bored I
del otro día o qué me tienen aburrid yo
uh things to scrape money to make
eh cosas para rascar dinero para llegar
ends meet because Talking about
a final de mes porque Hablando de ellos
themselves or making their own content they don't
mismos o haciendo contenido suyo no con
get visibility old that cat that's too
consiguen visibilidad antig eso gata eso
much I have doing other
está pasadísimo tengo haciendo otras
things without talking about my life or Yes if she
cosas sin hablar de mi vida ni Sí si
put something she celebrates the triumphs of others
puso algo celebra los triunfos de otros
as if they were hers well This was not
como si fueran suyos bueno Esto no fue
exactly what I put no Karime or rather
exactamente lo que puse no Karime o sea
what sounds familiar to me is that she celebrated
lo que me suena es que ella celebraba
the demands not the triumphs I mean
las demandas no los triunfos O sea que
she celebrated for example that someone
ella celebraba por ejemplo que alguien
put me that her friend put a
me pusiera que su amiga pusiera una
demand as if it were a demand that
demanda como si fuera una demanda que
she put you know she lived it as if it
ella ha puesto sabes la vivía como si
were hers that you Rejoice in  the
fuera de ella que tú te Alegres de las
things that happen to people who are on
cosas que le pasan a la gente que son de
your side that you consider that you are
tu bando que tú consideras que eres
part of something good is fine is fine
parte de algo bueno está bien está bien
you are happy about what you believe
tú te alegras de lo que tú crees que que
is justice but of course you know
es la justicia pero claro que tú sabes
the lies I mean the problem Patrick
las mentiras o sea el problema Patrick
is that you know what lies are the
es que tú sabes lo que son mentiras las
things that are lies and and you continue to
cosas que son mentiras y Y sigues las
lie knowing that they are lies let's see
mentiras sabiendo que son mentiras a ver
throwing that in our faces or taking it as mockery
echar eso en cara o tomarlo como burla
is to be a deep imbecile and a bad
es de ser imbécil profundo y mala
person no no it is to be no no no it's not that I
persona no no es de ser no no no es que
celebrate what I find pathetic is that
celebre lo que me parece patético es que
you celebrate the lawsuits as if they were
tú celebras las demandas como si fueran
yours you know as if you were going to win it
tuyas sabes como si la fueras a ganar tú
as you feel it like a triumph of yours no no
como lo sientes como un triunfo tuyo no
that you are happy for her Which
no que te alegres por ella Que también
is also logical it's normal the one who cried with
es Lógico es normal el que lloró de
emotion when a favorable sentence came out in favor
emoció cuando salió una sentencia
of her master is that already the
favorable a su amo es que ya lo de la
lady speaking to me like like a
señora hablándome como como como un
Wilson like a canine javir or something like
Wilson como un javir canino o algo de
that you know is like your master By the way
eso sabes es como tu amo Por cierto
annulled Yes annulled and then and then they
anulada Sí anulada y luego y luego la la
put the sentence back I mean what
volvieron a poner la sentencia O sea qué
sense Ah well Okay  It's true, it's true, it's
sentido Ah bueno Vale verdad es verdad
true that the sentence has been annulled, it
verdad que esa sentencia está anulada no
's not like the D won again by
es como que luego el D la volvió a ganar
talking about others, I don't need it.
hablando de los demás no lo necesito Por
Therefore, I'm not going to sell my private life
lo cual no voy a vender mi vida privada
here, nor are my friends going to do it.
por aquí ni mis amigos lo van a hacer
They said that I've been pregnant, that I had an
han dicho que he estado embarazada que
abortion, and my mother held my
he abortado y mi madre Me aguantaba la
skirt up, and it wasn't because it was windy and my
falda y no era porque hacía vient y se
panties were showing, but because I wouldn't
me vian las bragas sino porque no vaya
fall and lose the baby, a
ser que me caiga y pierda el bebé
million things, it's that I don't know who
millones de cosas es que yo no sé quién
said those things. The truth is, I mean, but it
ha dicho esas cosas La verdad O sea pero
's that I haven't
es que yo de cuentas de salseo no he
seen anyone saying anything about gossip, about
visto a nadie diciendo nada de eso de
pregnancy, about I don't know what you know, I mean, I have
embarazo de no sé qué sabes o sea yo eso
n't seen that.
no lo he visto
[Music]
[Música]